哦,小班困了
Oh,here's little Ben falling asleep.
等一下,他就要睡着了
A little bit later. Is he gonna sleep?
他要睡了吗?要睡了吗?
Is he gonna sleep? Is he gonna?
是的,就是这个了!
Yep,out like a light!
这一定是“他筋疲力竭了”系列的王牌了
This sure trumps the "Has he pooped?" series.
罗斯,我们爱他,好吗?
Ross,we love him,okay?
但是现在他只是一个裸体的胖小伙
But right now he's just a little fat guy.
我们太兴奋了吧?
How excited can we get?
-你拿的什么? -班的400张照片
-What you got? -400 pictures of Ben on a rug.
-哦,天哪! -让我看看!
-Oh,my God! -Let me see!
六人行 第1季 第24集 瑞秋恍然大悟
The One Where Rachel Finds Out
小班睡着了
Here's little Ben nodding off.
看莫妮卡姑姑的小男孩
Look at Aunt Monica's little boy!
-瞧,他有罗斯的发型. -我看看
-Look,he's got Ross haircut. -Let me see.
天啊,真可爱
Oh,God! Is he just the sweetest thing?
你一定想吻遍他
You must just wanna kiss him all over.
那感觉一定很好
That would be nice.
-什么? -没事
-Pardon? -Nothing.
只是嘴里有多余的空气
Just a little extra air in my mouth.
钱德,愿意帮我吗?我保证一定会还的
Chan,can you help me out? I'll pay you back.
好,包括上星期的威化饼,你现在欠我
Right. Including the waffles last week,you now owe me...
17美元
... 17 jillion dollars.
-真的,这一次我真的会还 -钱将从哪儿来?
-Really,I'll pay you back this time. -Where's this money coming from?
我正帮纽约大学医学院做一些研究
I'm helping out at the NYU Med School with research.
什么研究?
What kind of research?
只不过,你知道的,科学研究
Just,you know,science.
科学?
Science.
我想我听说过
Yeah,I think I've heard of that.
生殖研究
It's a fertility study.
乔伊,请告诉我你只贡献时间
Joey,please tell me you're only donating your time.
事实上,比这稍微多一点点
Actually,a little more than that.
谢谢,上帝.这会给我们带来更多笑料
Thank you,God. This will bring us so much joy.
拜托,这没什么了不起的
Come on,it's not that big a deal.
我只是两天去一趟
I just go down there every other day...
对此计划贡献己力
...and make my contribution to the project.
但两周后我就有七百元
But at the end of two weeks,I get $700!
你很快就可以轻松赚钱了
You're gonna be making money hand over fist.
这太有趣了,非常有趣
That's funny. Very funny.
太好了,我真的知道有人非常喜欢他们做的
This is great. I actually know somebody who loves what they do.
但是一天的辛苦工作后,你怎么放松自己呢?
But what do you do to unwind after a tough day at work?
我们有酸卷心菜丝,小面包
Okay,we got the coleslaw and buns.
还有绞牛肉及火鸡肉
The ground-up flesh of formerly cute cows and turkeys.
我喜欢和你一起出去烤肉
I just love barbecuing with you.
男人来了
Men are here!
我们生火
We make fire.
煮肉
Cook meat.
然后撒尿熄火,从此成为被拒绝的客人
Put out fire by peeing,no get invited back.
真逗
Cute.
-玛莲妮来电话说她会迟到. -好
-Melanie called. She'll be late. -Okay.
你们俩进展得如何?她会成为你的特殊女友吗?
How are things going? Is she becoming your "special someone"?
我不知道,她很好
I don't know. She's pretty great.
是吗?她对你的研究计划有何感想?
What does she think of your little science project?
你认为我会告诉她,我也和“杯子”约会?
You think I'd tell a girl I like that I'm also seeing a cup?
男人是有重点的
Man's got a point.
麻烦的是她想和我做爱
The tough thing is,she really wants to have sex.
这娘儿们疯了
Crazy bitch.
此计划我只剩一星期,根据规定
I got a week left to go. According to the rules...
如果我想拿到钱,我就不能做“个人”实验 如果你们懂我意思的话
... I can't conduct personal experiments,if you know what I mean.
乔伊,我们永远都了解你
Joey,we always know what you mean.
你以为烤肉会维持多久?
How long did you think this barbecue would last?
-我要去中国了 -天呐，你说一件事…
-I'm going to China. -Jeez,you say one thing,and....
-你要去中国? -对,为博物馆出差,有人找到骨头
-China? -For the museum. Someone found a bone.
我们要骨头,但他们不想给我们骨头
They don't want us to have it.
因此派我去说服他们给我们骨头,都是骨头的事
I'm going to try to persuade them. It's a whole big bone thing.
总之,我要去一个星期
Anyway,I'll be gone for a week.
你们将联络不到我,这是我的行程表
If you want to reach me,you can't. So here's my itinerary.
-这是我的照片. -让我看
-Here's a picture of me. -Oh,let me see.
能偶尔拿照片到卡萝家去给班看吗? 这样他就不会忘记我了
Could you show it to Ben every now and then so he doesn't forget me?
班,我是你爸爸
"Hi,Ben. I'm your father."
我是头
"I am The Head!"
这回烤肉一定很好玩
This barbecue's gonna be very fun.
瑞秋在吗?我想在我离开前祝她生日快乐
I wanted to wish Rachel a happy birthday before I left.
-她和卡尔在外面喝酒 -卡尔是谁?
-She's out having drinks with Carl. -Hey,who's Carl?
她在咖啡屋认识的那个
That guy she met at the coffeehouse.
-这个人是她在…? -咖啡屋?是的
-There's this guy she met at -The coffeehouse? Right.
这么说你知道他是谁
So you do know who he is.
我去跟他们道别
I'll go say goodbye to the guys.
告诉他们骨头的事吧
Hey,you know what? Tell them that bone story.
-我得到中国(瓷器)一趟 -国家?
-I have to go to China. -The country?
不,我妈家中的一大堆盘子
No,this big pile of dishes in my mom's breakfront.
你知道卡尔是谁吗?
Do you know who Carl is?
我想想看,艾文,赛门,希尔朵…不认识
Let's see. Alvin,Simon,Theodore.... No.
瑞秋今晚和他在一起喝酒
Rachel's having drinks with him tonight.
不,她还没对你有任何表示前,怎能这样做?
How can she,when she's never shown interest in you?
-忘了她吧 -他说得对
-Forget about her. -He's right.
去吧,到中国,吃中国菜
Please move on. Go to China. Eat Chinese food.
当然,他们在那儿只说“菜”
Of course,there they just call it "food."
是吗?大概吧,我也不知道
Yeah,I guess. I don't know.
帮我把这个交给她
All right,just give her this for me,okay?
兄弟,我们只是为你着想,我们要你快乐
We're looking out for you. We want you to be happy.
或许我喝了两瓶啤酒,但我爱你
I may only have a couple beers in me,but I love you.
我只喝了一瓶
I'm still on my first.
我觉得你人真好
I just think you're nice.
总之,我和朋友开始水果篮事业后
That's when we started this fruit basket business.
我们就自称为“三篮人”
We call ourselves "The Three Basketeers."
就像“三个火枪手”,只不过是用水果
Like "The Three Musketeers," only with fruit.
-谁想吃汉堡? -不,礼物先
-How do you want your burgers? -Presents first!
礼物先,待会儿再吃
We're doing presents first.
等等,猛男.进展得如何?
Hey,hold on there,tiger. How are you holding up?
不太顺利,她想在今晚
Well,not so good. She thinks tonight we're gonna...
就敲定这笔交易,如果你…你懂
...complete the transaction,if you know what And you do.
曾想过要为她服务吗?
Have you ever thought about being there for her?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
你知道的,只为她服务
You know,just be there for her.
不懂
Not following you.
考虑一下
Think about it.
我猜这是…
Okay. I'm guessing this is from....
-谢谢,玛莲妮. -这是我送你的
-Thank you,Melanie. -This one right here is from me.
好轻,还有声音
Okay. It's light. It rattles.
这是…
It's...
…是旅游拼字
...Travel Scrabble!
谢谢
Thank you.
这是乔伊送的
This one's from Joey.
感觉像是一本书,我猜是一本书,就是一本书啊!
It feels like a book,I think it's a book. And it's a book!
是“苏博士”（英国童话作家）
It's Dr. Seuss!
那本书让我度过许多难关
That book got me through some tough times.
这男人里面有个小孩
There's a little child inside this man.
医生说把他移走他就会死
The doctors say if they remove it,he'll die.
-这是谁送的? -罗斯送的
-Who's this from? -From Ross.
天啊,他记得
Oh,my God! He remembered!
-记得什么? -几个月前
-Remembered what? -lt was months ago.
我们经过一家古董店.我看见这个胸针时
We walked by this antique store. I saw this pin.
我告诉他我小时候我祖母也有一个
I told him it was like one my grandma had when I was little.
没想到他还记得
I can't believe he remembered!
但你能在飞机上玩吗?
Well,sure,but can you play it on a plane?
-好漂亮 一定花了他不少钱
It's so pretty! This must've cost him a fortune.
没想到他会这么做
I can't believe it.
记得大学时代他和卡萝相恋时
Remember when he fell in love with Carol...
他送她一只贵死人的水晶鸭吗?
...and bought her that expensive crystal duck?
你刚说什么?
What did you just say?
水晶鸭
Crystal duck.
不,相恋那一部份
No,no,no. The "love" part?
-天啊! -糟了,糟了
-Oh,my God! -Oh,no,no,no.
很好,继续挠你的头,时间会倒流的
That's good. Just keep rubbing your head. That'll turn back time.
太不可思议了,真是太不可思议了
This is unbelievable. I mean,this is unbelievable!
我知道,这真是太大了
I know. This is really,really huge.
不,它又小又细又霉
No,it's not. It's small. It's tiny. It's petite. It's wee.
我认为我们的生活将产生变化
I don't think any of our lives will ever be the same ever again.
这女人身上有消音装置吗?
Is there a mute button on this woman?
我认为这样很好啊,你和罗斯
I think this is so great. I mean,you and Ross!
-你有感觉吗? -没有
-Did you have any idea? -No,none!
我来到纽约的第一夜,他曾提过要约我出去
My first night in the city,he mentioned asking me out...
但他后来再没提过邀我出去
... but nothing ever happened.
他还说些什么?,他想约我出去?
What else did he say? Does he wanna go out?
如果他爱你爱得无法自拔
Given that he's in love with you...
他大概想和你喝杯咖啡什么的
... he wouldn't mind getting a cup of coffee.
罗斯?这些日子以来?我得找他谈谈
Ross? All this time? I've gotta talk to him.
-可他现在中国! -是“国家”
-He's in China! -The country.
她的飞机起飞了吗?
Is his flight gone?
是的!他正在看一个女人做这个:（空姐的手势）
Yes! He's watching a woman do this:
他走了!
He's gone!
他的飞机再过45分钟才会起飞
His flight doesn't leave for 45 minutes.
-时差呢? -从这儿到机场? -没错
-What about time difference? -From here to the airport?
-你赶不上的! -我得试试
-You'll never make it! -I've gotta try.
瑞秋,你要对他说什么?
What'll you say to him?
-我也不知道 -那么或许你不该去
-I don't know. -Then you shouldn't go.
没错,如果你是去伤他的心,不妨再等等
Right. If you're gonna break his heart,that can wait.
对,但如果是好消息,你得立刻去
But if it's good,tell him now.
-或许见到面时我就知道 -这个有帮助吗?
-Maybe I'll know when I see him. -All right,does this help?
没有,我只知道我等不了一星期,这件事太严重了
No. Look,all I know is,I cannot wait a week. This is just too big.
我得和他谈谈,再见了
I've just gotta talk to him. Okay,I'll see you later.
瑞秋,我爱你.先跟我把事情解决
Rachel,I love you! Deal with me first!
（中国话）再见  我的方针是……
好吧
All right.
（中国话）你笑什么
-罗斯,抱歉 -请出示登机证
-Ross! Excuse me,pardon me. -Your boarding pass?
我没有,我只是想找我朋友
I need to talk to my friend.
抱歉,除非有登机证,否则不能进入
Sorry,you're not allowed here without a pass.
他就在那儿,穿蓝色夹克
He's right there,in the blue jacket! Can l?
对不起,不行,联邦法规
I'm sorry. Federal regulations!
好吧,能否请你传话给他?
Then could you please just give him a message for me?
-这件事非常重要 -好吧,请说
-This is very important. -All right. What's the message?
我也不知道
I don't know.
抱歉,先生!有人叫我传话给你
Excuse me,sir! Excuse me,sir? I have a message for you.
是瑞秋!她说她喜欢你送的礼物 你回来后她想见你
Rachel loved the present. She'll see you when you get back.
什么?
What?
桃伊,拜托,我不懂她在说什么
Toby,I don't know what she's talking about.
我不认识瑞秋,别给我脸色看
There's no Rachel. Don't give me that deep freeze.
哦,乔伊,乔伊,乔伊!
Oh,Joey,Joey,Joey!
我想我爽昏了啊
I think I blacked out there for a minute.
这不算什么
It was nothing.
现在让我来伺候你
Well,now we gotta find something fun for you.
你知道吗?
You know what?
别管我了,我再伺候你一回
Forget about me. Let's give you another turn.
-又是我? -当然,有何不可?
-Me,again? -Sure. Why not?
明天有人会收到大水果篮!
Boy,somebody's gonna get a big fruit basket tomorrow!
我得告诉你,你不像我想像中的那样
I gotta tell you,you are nothing like I thought you'd be.
什么意思?
How do you mean?
大概是我认为,你是只顾自己享受的人
I had you pegged as a guy who's always,"Me,me,me!"
但你是个乐于付出的人
But you,you're a giver.
你是我见过最慷慨的人
You're the most generous man I ever met.
你简直就是个女人
I mean,you're practically a woman.
-你只是说说而已吧 -不
-You're just saying that. -No.
一个女人
A woman!
-怎么样? -我错过了
-So? -I missed him.
-很遗憾 -这太糟了
-I'm so sorry. -That's too bad.
是啊
Yeah,right.
不,我觉得对她不好,我真的这么认为
No,I feel bad for her. I do.
我可以考虑其他人多过考虑我自己
I can think of somebody other than myself.
好吧,我要去睡觉了
All right,I'm going to bed.
-生日快乐.保持状态 -谢谢
-Happy birthday. Hang in there. -Thanks.
好啊!
Yes!
披萨优惠券
Pizza coupons.
你们打算帮忙清理这里吗?
Okay. You guys want help cleaning up this mess?
不错
That'd be great.
瑞秋,这包装纸要留下来吗?
So,Rach,you wanna save this wrapping paper?
你要为罗斯留下,还是要我丢掉?
Are you gonna go for it with Ross or should I throw it out?
我不知道,我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
我左思右想
Thought about it all the way there...
我左思右想,你知道的,罗斯
...and I thought about it all the way back. You know,it's Ross!
你知道我什么意思?就是罗斯
You know what I mean? It's Ross.
-当然! -当然
-Sure! -Sure.
我不知道,这是我内心深处的感受
I don't know. This is just my initial gut feeling...
我想这样应该会很不错
... but I'm thinking it'd be really great.
天啊,我也是这样想 这样我们就成了亲戚兼朋友
Oh,my God,me too! We'd be like friends-in-law!
你知道最棒的是什么?最棒的就是你已对他了如指掌
The best part is you already know all about him.
就好像从第15次约会开始
You start on the 1 5th date.
对,但这就像从第15次约会开始
But it would be like starting on the 1 5th date.
这观点也不错
Another good point.
不,在第15次约会时,感情已
I mean,on the 1 5th date,you're already in a very...
相当深厚,你们已经定下来了
... "relationship-y" place. You're committed.
如果感情破裂该怎么办?
What happens if it doesn't work out?
-为何会感情破裂? -有时候是这样的
-Why isn't it working out? -Sometimes it doesn't.
你不觉得他帅?他钱赚得不够多?
Is he not cute enough? Does he not make enough money?
-不,我只是 -或许是另有其人?
-No,I'm just -Maybe there's someone else.
-另有其人? -没有,没有另有其人
-ls there someone else? -No,there is no one else.
那么你为何甩掉我哥?
Then why are you dumping my brother?
大…挥霍者
Hey,big Spender!
她还在睡觉
She's still asleep.
-情况如何? -你有没有老觉得自己床上功夫不错?
-So how'd it go? -You know how you think you're great?
你会问这种问题,表示你根本不了解我
The fact you'd even ask shows how little you know me.
昨晚我不能做让自己满足的事
Last night I couldn't do the thing that usually makes me great.
因此我得搬出全套功夫
So I had to do all this other stuff.
结果我得到什么回应?
And the response I got! Man,oh,man!
就像是盛大的游行
It was like a ticker-tape parade!
我明白,游行发生时,我的房间非常接近游行路线
I know. My room's very,very close to the parade route.
这简直是太神奇了,而且不只是对她,对我也一样
It was amazing,and not just for her. For me too!
我就好像突然失明
It's like,all of a sudden I'm blind...
但其他的感官却更加的敏感
... but all my other senses are heightened.
好像我达到…
It's like I was able to appreciate it...
…更高的境界
...on another level.
-我不知道你还有更高的境界. -我懂,我自己也不知道
-I didn't know you had another level. -I know. Neither did l!
现在橙汁有活动吗?
Is something going on with O.J.?
漂亮的裙子,生日礼物?
Hey,great skirt. Birthday present?
-谁送的? -你
-From who? -You.
我将你送的衬衫改成的
I exchanged the blouse you got me.
真聪明
Well,it's the thought.
罗斯的飞机不是再过几小时就要抵达? 27-b通道?
Doesn't Ross'flight get in in a couple hours? At gate 27B?
对,莫妮卡,我一直在想
Yeah. Monica,you know,I've been thinking about it.
我虽决定和罗斯在一起,但这样或许不好
I've decided this Ross thing is not a good idea.
为什么?
Why?
因为我感觉,我不只是和他出去
I feel like I wouldn't just be going out with him.
而是和你们大家一起出去,因为压力…
I'd be going out with all of you. There'd be pressure
不,没有压力.没有压力…
No pressure,no pressure!
什么都还没发生呢，你就…
Nothing has happened,and you're already so
我没有,开始我也觉得有点奇怪
I'm not "so." Okay,I was a teensy bit weird at first...
但我没事的,我保证
... but I'll be good. I promise.
-是谁? -是我,卡尔
-Who is it? -It's me,Carl.
-上来! -背着我哥做这种事?
-Come on up. -Behind my brother's back?
我就做不出这种疯狂事
Is the kind of crazy thing you won't be hearing from me.
-七百块! -你办到了!
-Seven hundred bucks! -All right,you did it!
我们有水果可吃吗?
Do we have any fruit?
折腾了两星期
Man,hell of a two weeks.
我感觉自己学到了一些
You know what? I feel I learned something.
这么说你将继续“完全为她”?
You'll stick with this "all for her" thing?
你疯了不成
What are you,crazy?
瞎人重新见光明后还会这样走路吗?
When a blind man gets his sight back,does he walk around like this?
我是说如果我再看见艾德贝格拉二世（演员，环保主义者领袖）
If I see one more picture of Ed Begley Jr...
在那电车上,我就举枪自尽
...in that stupid electric car,I'm gonna shoot myself!
别误会我的意思,我个人并不反对环保
I'm not against environmental issues,per se...
只是我讨厌那家伙
...it's just that guy!
我难以相信你跟他约会,而不是跟我
I can't believe you'd rather go out with him than me.
抱歉,我正在约会
Excuse me,I'm trying to have a date here.
行,那就别再想我
Fine. Just stop thinking about me.
办不到,对不?
Can't do it,can you?
我想你,那又怎样?
I'm thinking about you. So what?
我不懂你为何会选上这种人?
I don't get it. What do you see in this guy?
他像是个好男人
Happens to be a very nice guy.
老兄,买台真正的车吧
I mean,come on,buddy! Get a real car!
瑞秋,给我一个机会吧
Rachel,come on. Give us a chance.
罗斯,太难了
Ross,it's too hard.
为什么?因为大家会感觉不对劲?这是我们两人的事
Why,because it'll get weird for everyone else? This is about us.
我从九年级开始就爱上你
I've been in love with you since the ninth grade.
罗斯,你像是我最要好的朋友 如果分手我将失去你
You're like my best friend. If we broke up,and I lost you
不,你为何认为我们会分手?
What makes you think that?
曾和你在一起的人不是都和你分手了？
Have you been involved where you haven't broken up?
不
No.
但这种事只会发生一次
But it only has to happen once.
你我都知道我们是天生的一对
You and I both know we are perfect for each other. Right?
唯一的问题是:你对我有感觉吗?
So the only question is: Are you attracted to me?
我不知道
I don't know.
我从未以那种方式看你
I mean,I've never looked at you that way before.
那就开始看吧
Well,start looking.
-喔. -的确!
-Wow. -Exactly!
没错,我就是那个
And I'm gonna be the guy...
被困在交通事故中的家伙
...caught behind this hammerhead in traffic!
对…你是对的
Right! You're right.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我本应该去机场接朋友
I'm supposed to pick up a friend at the airport.
真是抱歉
I am so sorry!
如果你想在这儿继续喝,请便
If you wanna finish your drinks,please do.
-但我得走了,抱歉 -可是
-I'm sorry,I gotta go. I'm sorry. -But....
-你要去哪? -去接罗斯
-Where are you going? -To get Ross.
-天哪,这太令人兴奋了! -我知道
-My God,this is so exciting! -I know.
你是否愿意继续我剩下的约会？我继续不下去了
If you want the rest of my date,I'm not gonna finish it.
-瑞秋,他不是三明治. -不,他是一个有两张剧院门票的银行家
-Rachel,he's not a sandwich. -No,he's a banker with opera tickets.
你好!
Hello!
-你要去哪? -机场
-Where you going? -Airport.
你不能告诉他,有太多的事情我没有去做
You can't tell him. There's so much I haven't done.
我还没有看《海滩游侠》呢!
I haven't watched Baywatch with Yasmine Bleeth!
钱德,轻松点,这是一个好的接机
Chandler,relax. This is a good going to the airport.
哦,好吧,飞吧,好女人,像风一样飞吧
Oh,well then fly,good woman,fly like the wind.
-我在飞! -告诉他是我吹的风!
-I'm flying! -Tell him I'm the one who blew it!
好吧,另外一个爱情博士的成功案例
Yes,another successful case for the love doctor.
对不起!对不起
Excuse me! Pardon me. Excuse me. Sorry.
桃伊,别再胡思乱想了
Toby,for God's sake,will you let it go?
没有瑞秋这个人
There's no Rachel!
嘿,我拿到了
Hey! I got that.
-谢谢 -不客气
-Thanks,sweetie. -No problem.
我迫不及待想将你介绍给我朋友
I can't wait for you to meet my friends.
你不认为他们会评断我、取笑我?
You don't think they'll judge me?
-他们会的,我只是… -等不及
-No,they will. I just.... -Can't wait!
他们一定会喜欢你的
Come on,they're gonna love you.